Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan,CA; Camp Haan; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Fort Meade,MD; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan,CA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Irwin,CA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan,CA; Los Angeles; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Deslauries, Joseph, undated; Camp Haan,CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dettrich, William, undated; Jacksonville; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Elizabeth M, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Elizabeth M, undated; Fort Oglethorpe; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Elizabeth M, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Elizabeth M, undated; Fort Des Moines; IA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Bessie, undated; Fort des Moines; See Elizabeth M; Awarded Good Conduct Medal; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Bessie, undated; See Elizabeth M; Awarded Good Conduct Medal-WAC; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Bessie, undated; Fort des Moines; See Elizabeth M; Awarded Good Conduct Medal; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Bessie, undated; See Elizabeth M; Awarded Good Conduct Medal-WAC; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, Elizabeth M, undated; Parents; Left for WAC Training; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Devlin, James F., undated; Private; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Dick, Eugene V, undated; St Petersburg; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dick, James W, undated; California; Coast Guard; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dick, James W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Wife Doris,112 High St; Coast Guard,Son of Mr and Mrs James Dick; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dick, James W, undated; Pacific Theater; Description of Service in Navy; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; Belgium; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickinson, Leon C, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickson, William A, undated; 7th Army; Germany; Description of Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dickson, William A, undated; 7th Army; Germany; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - DiMauro, Carmel A, undated; Maui; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dimock, Gordon H, undated; Camp Howze,TX; Texas; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dintsch, Edward M, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dobosz, Frank L, undated; APO NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dobosz, Frank L, undated; APO NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dobosz, Frank L, undated; APO NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dobosz, John A, undated; North Africa; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dobosz, Frank L, undated; Tom Regan; Promoted; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Doherty, Joseph A., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Domain, Donald A, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Domback, Edward J, undated; 43rd Infantry; Philippines; Interviewed About Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dombroski, Leon B, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dombroski, Leon B, undated; Honolulu; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowd, Francis, undated; Moody Field; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowd, Francis, undated; Moody Field; Paterson, NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowd, Francis, undated; Moody Field; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowd, Francis, undated; New Address, Mrs Dowd; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowding, Kenneth, undated; Okinawa; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowgiewicz, Anthony S., undated; Oahu; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowgiewicz, Leonard P, undated; Seymour Johnson Field; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dowgiewicz, Anthony S., undated; New Address, Viva Dougiewicz; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Downhan, Wesley P, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Gulfport; MS; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Guam; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Chicago,IL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Duell, Ralph, undated; Corpus Christi,TX; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Dunay, John, undated; 5th Infantry; Luxembourg; Description of Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - DuPaul, Edward, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - DuPrey, Roy H, undated; Memphis; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - DuPrey, Roy H, undated; Sampson,NY; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - DuPrey, Roy H, undated; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Eastwood, Charles, undated; Scott Field; IL; See:Raymond Fahey and Tillman Cormier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edgerton, Eugene C, undated; England; Presented with Medal; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edgerton, Eugene C, undated; England; Presented with Medal; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edmondson, William, undated; AAF; Italy; Description of Air Supply,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Irwin E, undated; Camp Gordon; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Walter F, undated; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Walter F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Lawrence Street; Son of Mr and Mrs Walter Edwards; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Arthur E, undated; Ayer,MA; Camp Life; Fort Devens,MA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Arthur E, undated; Fort Devens,MA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Arthur E, undated; Camp Keyes,ME; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Arthur E, undated; Amhurst,MA; Scenery; Acadia National Park, Bar Harbor, ME; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Edwards, Calvin S, undated; Italy; Served Engineer Unit with Rockville Men; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ehret, Edward R, undated; USS Terror; Pacific; Serving on Mine Layer; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Einsiedel, Elwin G, undated; Fort Ord; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Einsiedel, Elwin G, undated; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Elderkin, George, undated; Fort jackson; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Elderkin, George, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Elderkin, George, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellis, Roderick J, undated; Hospital; England; Recovering From Combat Wound; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Arlington Farms; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Bronx,NY; Camp Life; Hunter College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Stillwater,OK; City Life; A. and M. College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Robert M, undated; Santa Ana,CA; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Mrs Mason Ellsworth; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Robert M, undated; Mrs Mason Ellsworth; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ellsworth, Betty R, undated; Naval Barracks; NY; Discharge Questionaire,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Endore, Pierre, undated; Camp Endicott,RI; Seabees; 9 Post Cards of Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Engley, Frank B, undated; Carlisle Barracks; PA; Graduated Medical Field School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Ernest, undated; Sicily; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Erwin L, undated; Fort Lee; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Erwin L, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Ernest, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 17 Chamberlain Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Walter, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 17 Chamberlain Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Erwin L, undated; New York,NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Ernest E, undated; 12th Army Air Force; Received Medal, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Erismann, Ernest E, undated; 12th Army Air Force; B-25 Base; Bomb Group Achieved Record for Accuracy; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ertel, Thomas, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 29 Vernon Avenue; Small Photo 12/18/1943; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ertel, William C, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ertel, Vincent G., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Factor, Morris L, undated; Maxwell Field; AL; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fagan, Wayne R, undated; Mrs Fagan; Military Record, Photo; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fahey, Raymond, undated; Scott Field; IL; See:Charles Eastwood and Tillman Cormier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fahey, James, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fahey, Raymond, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Prospect Street; Stationed India; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fahey, James, undated; European Theater; Service as Ordnance Man; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fahy, Bernard, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farnham, Woodrow F, undated; Mrs Woodrow Farnham; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farnham, Woodrow F, undated; 95th Infantry; Germany; Earned Medal,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farnham, Woodrow F., undated; Staff Sargeant; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Henry A, undated; Enclosure; Swannanoa, GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Larry, undated; South Pacific; letter from Howard delBene/Alvin J Usher; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Henry A "Red", undated; Swannanoa, NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Henry A "Red", undated; Swannanoa, NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Henry, undated; Swannanoa, NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farr, Lawrence, undated; Lake Placid; NY; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Farrington, George, undated; West Road,; Ellington; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fecteau, Oscar A, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Felber, Everett, undated; Virginia Beach; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Felden, Curt, undated; APO 182A; Los Angeles, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Felden, Curt, undated; Holland; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ferguson, Roy C Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ferguson, Roy C Jr, undated; Luke Field; AZ; Finished Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ferguson, Whitney, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Ferris, George H, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fetko, Joseph F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Filip, Francis, undated; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finance, Edward, undated; Apo New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finance, Edwin, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finance, Eddie, undated; Pyote,TX; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W Jr, undated; Manicani Island; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W Jr, undated; Newport News; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W Jr, undated; Newport News; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W, undated; Newport News,VA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W, undated; Mrs Margaret Finley; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Finley, Clarence W, undated; Shoemaker; CA; Discharged, Miltary Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fish, Henry Bernard, undated; Mansfield Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Aviation Cadet USNR; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisher, Arthur E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisher, Arthur E, undated; Selman Field; Monroe, LA; Commissioned; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisher, Arthur E, undated; San Antonio; TX; Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisher, Norman, undated; San Antonio; TX; Letter to Journal; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisk, Douglas, undated; Belgium; With Poem; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisk, Douglas, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisk, Douglas, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fisk, Douglas, undated; Belgium; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Flamm, Wilton E, undated; Manila; Awaiting Assignment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Flechsig, Carlton A, undated; McChord Field; WA; Thanks for the Journal; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fleischer, Kenneth, undated; New London; CT; Fire Fighter in Sub Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fleischer, Raymond W, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Student at Navy Pacific University; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fleisher, Raymond W, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Florence, Oline, undated; Paris,TX; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fluckiger, Walter, undated; Guadalcanal; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fluckinger, Walter, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Forster, George B, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Member of Alert Detatchment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Forster, George B, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Forster, George B, undated; 8th Air Force; England; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fox, William G., undated; Private First Class; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Francis, Arthur, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Freedman, Aaron, undated; Netherlands; East Indies; Connecticut Soldiers in Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Frey, Leo J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Irving, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Irving, undated; Italy; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Irving, undated; Italy; City Life; Palermo,Catacombe dei Cappuccini; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Irving, undated; Atlanta,GA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, undated; Gabes; Scenery; Oasis; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Irving, undated; Africa; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedman, Rose, undated; Naval Barracks; NY; Discharge Questionaire,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedreich, R., undated; APO 528 New York; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedreich, Herbert H, undated; Camp Endicott; Davisville, RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedrich, Herbert H, undated; San Fransisco,CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedrich, Herbert H, undated; Hawaii; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedrick, Herbert H., undated; Hawaii; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Friedrick, Herbert H, undated; Camp Peary,VA; Seabees; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Fuller, Harold, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Discharged; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Moses Lake; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; APO 520; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; MacDill Field; Tampa, FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Moses Lake; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Francis S, undated; Camp Haan; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; FortGeorgeWright,WA; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Fort George Wright,WA; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; FortGeorgeWright,WA; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Futoma, Edward A, undated; 15th AAF; Italy; Description of Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gagne, Simeon, undated; San Fransisco; CA; Home From Pacific with Photo; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gailbraith, Robert A, undated; Fort Belvoir; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gakeler, George H, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Galbraith, Robert A, undated; Fort Belvoir; VA; Discharge Form; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gallup, Francis C, undated; 15th AAF; Italy; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Garczynaki, R.A., undated; Harding Field,LA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gardner, George C, undated; Western Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gardner, George C, undated; Mrs Mason Ellsworth; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gauthier, Henry, undated; Manila; Philippines; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gebhardt, Roy, undated; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Geissler, Francis E, undated; Camp Craft; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Geissler, Francis E, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Geissler, Francis E, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Genovesi, Carlo, undated; Nashville; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Genovesi, Carlo, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; Fort Custer; MI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; Fort Lewis; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; Camp Grant; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Emanuel, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; France; Son of Mr and Mrs Ernest Gerber,Davis Ave; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerber, Ralph E, undated; Home on Furlough; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gergler, Wayne N, undated; Western Front; Awarded Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerwinski, Joseph, undated; Wilmington, DE; Center Dining Car; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerwolls, Otto Jr, undated; Alamagordo; NM; Military Record, Unusual Size; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerwolls, Otto Jr, undated; Alamagordo; NM; Article About Height; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gerwolls, Otto Jr, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gesm, Neal, undated; Germany; City Life; See Gunn, Neal; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gess, William, undated; Discharged,Mrs Wm H Gess; F-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Andrew, undated; Apo New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Charles M, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Emil J, undated; Camp Ripley; Little Falls, MN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Hong Kong; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Boston; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Lion; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Boston; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Subic Bay; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Louis H, undated; Samar; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Gessay, Emil J, undated; Little Falls, MN; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)